You monsters!
Don't turn your backs on me!
Find it!
I'll favor this one!
Hamon Baby Launcher!
Thank you.
I'll be in love with the enemy.
I'll be in love with the lack of hope.
I'll be in love with you.
Could this be...
is this what I think? Nice work!
Caesar may be a narcissist,
but his Hamon skills are solid.
These bubbles may look harmless,
but prepare for a bombardment!
He...
he popped them all.
How on earth did he do that?
That's not his hair.
Those are wires attached to
his head he's manipulating.
He pumped my bubbles with
the wind that they created.
But then that means they were
designed to be anti-Harmon weapons.
Somehow they're already familiar
with the principles of Harmon.
They must have faced Harmon at
some point over 2,000 years ago.
What is that?
What's happening to the air around them?
Caesar, look out! Get down!
What the...
Cover your eyes!
That wasn't just wind,
it was the aftermath of a powerful
vortex that's still active!
Caesar!
These humans know Hamon.
I thought we destroyed all the members of
the Hamon tribe two thousand years ago.
And yet, here they are, ready to
welcome us at our own awakening.
Damn!
You killed him!
You killed my friend!
Do you think losing him high will stop me?
Stop!
Why are you laughing?
What's so funny?
You all have memorized your
Hamon handbook very well.
You always say the same thing.
It was that way when we crossed
from the western continent.
And it is that way now still.
Do you think losing an arm or
an eye or a leg will stop me?
How dare you take my friend's life?
Don't you know how much I loved him?
That's why we laugh,
human. You! You bastards!
Ignore him.
We're on a quest to find the stone.
What?
Where are you going?
Face me, cowards!
You're most vulnerable in
your throat and your lungs.
We know that if you can't breathe,
then your hormone is rendered useless.
But because I cannot resist
a worthy opponent, hear me.
I shall spare you because I long for the
opportunity to meet you
again when you are stronger.
The next time we meet, I
want to admire your strength.
I want you to become worthy of my time so
that I might destroy you with great honor.
It appears that he was
the only Hormone user.
Hmm, let's move.
Sorry, I just can't seem
to shake this cough.
Maybe it's the Hormone
training that's making me ill.
What do you think?
Hmm, he only sliced your eyelid.
The actual eyeball itself is just fine.
Perhaps you should sit this one out.
I think we've all seen enough of
the Bubble Launcher for one day.
Watch and learn as I take
care of this one myself!
JoJo!
Just calm down, Speedwagon.
This guy is asking for it.
It's time for me to show off the brand
new technique I've been working on.
What?
Please allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Joseph Joestar,
and these are the hands known for
defeating your mate-son Viento.
I call this move my hum-on-clacker volley.
I start off by filling these little
clacker balls here with a bit of Hamon.
Oh, no!
JoJo, what the hell do
you think you're doing?
This is no time for games.
What are you doing?
Are you trying to disrespect
my friend by playing the fool?
Not intentionally.
I'm trying to be serious.
Caesar, I am truly sorry
for the loss of your friend.
I understand both your
pain and your anger.
Additionally,
these guys may be the biggest group of
egotistical jackasses
I've ever seen in my life.
I may not be a master of this yet,
but I'll still knock you into next
Tuesday with my clacker volley!
I hate to admit it, but I know
that my Heaven is relatively weak.
I'm pretty sure I can make up for what
I'm lacking with these steel clackers
if I can just break open your scheme
even a little and fill you with Heaven.
That should even up my
handicap, don't you think?
I can tell you're nervous.
Take that!
Well, that was fun.
Let us keep moving.
Apparently, the human race has
regressed rather than evolved.
Quite an understatement.
Amusing, though.
Jojo, what are you doing?
Your child's little games are
going to get us all killed.
He's playing coy, but this may
actually be the best JoJo's got.
He'd be fine if he was facing
some common street punk,
but I don't think he realizes that these
opponents are on a
completely different level.
It would be comical if
it weren't so tragic.
Why isn't anyone taking my
little metal balls seriously?
That's far enough.
Don't make me clack you into the ground.
Stop.
Don't you feel that human
lives are short enough?
There's no need to sprint to your death.
Silence!
If you've ever had spaghetti on nero
de sepia, you know it looks bad,
but it's delicious.
You should taste my clacker
volley before you judge it.
The clackers, they vanished!
I've been training on my
harmon all the live long day.
He's insane!
Well, look at Ma, no hands.
Where are the clackers?
A true magician.
Never reveals his secrets! Ain't this!
How can anything move like that?
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
He's faster than San Viento.
I don't think those idiotic
clackers did so much as graze him.
I admire your weapon, your courage,
and your creativity, human.
I'm actually enjoying
your company you deserve
time one minute but only one that is how
much Time I will allow
you to fight the mighty
Wamuu I shall use your
wound as a timer your
wrist will work well
as a timekeeping device
and you will lose
consciousness due to a loss
of blood in exactly one
minute show me what you
can do human oh this is
what I often told the
members of the Hamon
tribe your life is now
my hourglass measured
in blood Wamuu we'll be
waiting outside now boy
go ahead and retrieve
your weapon quickly What
I'm sorry I'm growing
deaf in this ear it
almost sounded like you
said go ahead and
retrieve your weapon which
would be ridiculous I
mean why would you to
retrieve something that
comes right back to you.
Looks like my clack of
boomerang worked pretty well.
I shouldn't even need the full
minute to destroy you now.
That's for killing Caesar's friend.
That's for not taking me seriously.
And that's because I'm sick
of looking at your ugly face.
Do what you must.
I deserve as much.
No opponent has ever struck my face, and
this is the price for my carelessness.
I shall take this beating in order to
properly honor you before I destroy you.
You say that no one has ever hit
you in that ugly mug of yours?
What an honor!
You didn't even stop to blink when you
killed Caesar's friend, Mark, did you?
You monster!
Do you not value life at all?
Jojo, watch yourself!
His arm isn't broken!
He's getting ready to use it!
Whoa!
I have a feeling this isn't good for me.
A charming observation, human.
I'm now scarred due to my carelessness.
It was my duty to allow you to pummel me
as punishment for my own lack of judgment.
That has now ended, however.
Jojo, finish him now while you still can!
My ultimate technique,
the Divine Sandstorm!
I don't like the sound of that!
He starts by spinning
his left arm clockwise,
and then his right arm counter-clockwise.
Jojo is unprepared to
counter a technique like
this as Wamo's fists seem
to grow before his eyes.
The air between Whamu's arms transforms
into a powerful vortex of destruction.
This vacuum creates a highly
pressurized, deadly maelstrom.
Great, if he can tear
through marble pillars,
I don't see myself having much of a
chance against a windstorm like this.
I don't think I've ever
seen anything this powerful!
Jojo!
I call that Divine Sandstorm.
No! Jojo!
Don't be a damn fool!
Run, Speedwagon.
Get out of here before it's too late.
I'll try and distract him somehow.
Curse this blood in my eye.
Threw off my aim.
But it proved enough when you made
the choice to hide behind a pillar.
Hmm.
You died quickly.
Normally, I would ignore human
onlookers such as yourselves.
However,
you witnessed my shame, so unfortunately
I must take the time to destroy you both.
You may pray now if you wish.
Huh?
Hmm, must be the light.
What does he think he's doing?
I don't believe it.
He's actually trying to escape!
Huh? Hmm...
That coward has no shame
playing dead like that.
I understand leaving me,
but what about Speedwagon?
I knew he was spineless!
This guy is the most
powerful foe I've ever faced.
My breathing is out of control.
I can't control my Hamon.
I don't really have any other option left.
Luckily, my specialty is running away.
Behold, our now broken hero.
Jojo, forced to play dead,
crawling for his life, and now leaving
Speedwagon behind to face certain death.
Even with all of this, Jojo remains
dedicated, a hero worthy of this tale.
How is that, you ask?
Nice try there, human.
You coward.
No true warrior would ever feign
death just to save himself.
That may be true, though my intention
was not to escape but to distract.
Truth be told, I was just trying
to get you onto this minecart.
You are clever indeed.
So you were only playing the part of the
coward to lure me away from your friends,
is that right?
I'm surprised you fell for it.
That trick is probably older than you.
Get out now, speed wagon. Run!
Caesar, go!
What are you guys doing?
Jojo, that bastard.
What a noble move.
Now that I've painted
myself into a corner here,
I need to come up with a
second part to my plan,
which would be...
The unflappable hero.
He calmly searches for options,
not knowing what to do next,
but his will remains unbroken.
Jojo! No!
Damn you, Jojo!
He's in far worse shape than I am!
I should have been the
one to lure Wamuu away.
I see now that Jojo only acts
foolishly to confound his opponent.
He must actually have a good
plan to beat those monsters.
Although you are quite confident for
someone who is knocking on death's door?
I must tell you that
your plan is a poor one.
You're quite tough, I'll give you that.
Soft-headed, but tough nonetheless.
Tell me, how do you remain unyielding
in the moments before your death?
Is it because you have bricks for brains,
or do you still have another trick for me?
Do you really want to know?
Actually, no. Let me guess.
Because you're so obviously clever,
I'll give you the benefit of
the doubt that you wouldn't be
stupid enough to be holding a
stick of dynamite behind your back.
Damn, he's on to me!
And I know you wouldn't insult my
intelligence by thinking you could
quickly throw the brake and send
the minecart flying off the tracks.
Maybe like this!
Damn, he got me there too!
The time on your hourglass
wrist is just about up.
There is absolutely no chance that
you will survive this any longer.
I found your tricks to be very quaint.
Before you die, tell me, why do I
still not see defeat in your eyes?
I'll tell you if you want, but you're
going to have to say please first.
More games!
You've tested me long enough.
Prepare to die! Such a shame,
because a month from now I can guarantee
that I would be able to destroy you.
What was that?
With just one more month of
training, I would annihilate you.
I was the first person to hit as
well as the first to scar your face.
When I put my mind to something, I
can accomplish pretty much anything.
Oh, well, I guess none of
that really matters now.
So, can we just get this over with?
It will be an honor to be killed by
a warrior like you, blah, blah, blah.
What do you mean by this?
Oh, I'm sick and tired
of all this talking.
Just hurry up and make it painless, Wamu.
Explain yourself.
What are you trying to get at?
I don't know how, but he's still alive.
Is it true that you Pillar
Men often live for millennia?
That's a long time to be
walking around with the
shame of having your face
rearranged by a lowly human.
It seems to me that the only way
you could regain your honor would be
by defeating me in a fight after
I've undergone proper Hamon training.
I do not have to defeat you
in order to maintain my honor.
His entire body is shaking with rage.
I have a chance if I can make him
think his integrity is at stake.
He gave himself away as the proud warrior
type the moment he called me a coward.
Pride is his Achilles' heel.
I don't know if you noticed,
but I'm still new at this.
However, if I trained with
my harmon for a month,
I know I could give you the fair
fight a warrior like you deserves.
The first person who ever hit you
in the face gave you a nasty scar.
It would be a shame if you killed
that person before he's worthy.
But if you feel the need to kill me before
I have a chance to battle you as an equal,
then go ahead and do
whatever you need to do.
You bastard!
Mama.
Master ACDC.
You gave this human one minute.
Why must you insist on
letting him toy with you?
Just go away.
I almost had him.
Master ACDC, I have grown fond of this
particular member of the Hamon tribe.
I got him!
Jojo, you will be happy to know that I
have decided to accept your proposition.
If you swear that you will train your
hardest to fulfill your potential,
then I will give you
exactly one month to do so.
So you're not going to kill me now?
That's right.
But we're going to fight again. We are.
Are you sure you want to do this?
I'll give you a chance to take it back.
Yes, I can't believe it's working.
However, I will need assurances that you
will not try to run away again, of course.
Nice, Wamu.
I was wondering when you
would finally propose.
Say hello to the wedding ring of death.
Guess where it goes.
A hint not on your finger.
What are you doing with that?
This ring will start
to dissolve in 33 days.
It's impossible to remove, and once
dissolved, it will release a virulent poison.
Any attempt to remove or damage it
will also release the lethal poison.
However, there is one certain way
to dissolve the ring without harm.
Simply battle and defeat
me within 33 days,
and I shall give you the antidote that
I keep inside the hollow of my lip ring.
Jojo!
The vow on that wedding ring
states, Till death do us part, Jojo.
Be at the Coliseum in 33 days.
Meet me there at midnight, and
we shall battle as equals, Jojo.
I hope you didn't think your paltry
tricks would help you escape, human.
I don't imagine the two of us will fight,
but just in case, here's a gift for you.
One that fits perfectly
around your windpipe!
My heart and my throat!
My poison is quite different from Wamu's,
and I keep the antidote for
that poison in my nose ring.
Kars, would you like to go next?
I don't think so.
Immortality can be boring at times.
To encounter a worthy opponent, that is
both such a rare and tantalizing thought.
A gift that would give our lives meaning.
I can see why you do this.
However, do not forget that our goal
is to obtain the Red Stone of Asia.
We must stay focused. Let's go!
Train long and hard, Jojo, so you
can challenge my divine sandstorm!
I can't believe that.
Two wedding rings with poison?
Is that supposed to be some
kind of sick joke or something?
I've got one around my throat
and one around my heart.
Do these guys think I'm some
kind of bigamist or maybe...
Well, at least Speedwagon
and Caesar are safe.
That's what's important.
No sense in feeling sorry for myself.
Jojo, you fool.
That was one hell of a
bluff you just pulled there!
The best con man couldn't
have done it better than you.
You acted bravely, but now
you'll need to back it up.
We don't have much time to work.
And we have serious Hamon training ahead.
In and around the lake.
Mornings come out of the sky.
They stand there.
24 before my love?
I'll be there.
When I said I needed a month,
I only meant it as a blob!
Well, from up here, it's
really more deep than tall.
God, wait!
Please don't do this!
Because you're a girl doesn't mean
that I won't give you what you deserve.
Welcome to Venice.